杰基·罗宾逊第一个入场 然后是"棒球坏小子"艾迪·斯坦科
Jackie Robinson at first. "The Brat" Eddie Stanky at second.
第三个是斯派特·乔根森 紧接着是队长皮威·里斯
Spider Jorgensen at third. And the captain, Pee Wee Reese, at short.
球迷们 不管你问谁 他都会告诉你 吉列锋速剃须刀真是个宝贝
Fans, ask any man and they'll tell you, the Gillette Superspeed razor is a honey.
也许是你用过最好用的剃须刀
Maybe the sweetest shaving razor you'll ever use.
看起来犀利 摸起来犀利 你就是犀利哥
Look sharp, feel sharp, be sharp.
我们这儿不欢迎黑人!
We don't want no niggers here!
嘴长在他们身上 我们只管好好打球
They can say all they want. We're just here to play ball.
把他赶出球场!
Get him off the field!
他们只是一群还活在内战中的疯子
It's just a bunch of crackpots still fighting the Civil War.
如果把玉米杆拔出来当武器 我们本可以打败北方那些混蛋的
Well, we'd have won that son of a gun if the cornstalks would have held out.